aaa-calif.com 2009-12-18

# Privacy Notice - Automobile Club of Southern California

## Privacy Notice

The Auto Club and its affiliates respect your privacy. We want to assure you that safeguarding information about you is important to us. We gather nonpublic personal information about you to conduct business on your behalf, provide superior service, and communicate offers on products and services that we believe will be of interest or benefit to you.

**Information we collect.** We collect, from you or other sources, information such as your name, address and telephone number. We also collect information about your transactions with us, with our affiliates, or with others, such as purchases related to the use of your membership card. Some information is accessible by you for your review and modification on our web site. Changing any personal information requires that you log in with a unique user name and password created by you. 

**Information we share.** We share information about you with our affiliates and non-affiliates, such as companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. Because we value the trust you’ve placed in us, we require that these companies keep the information we send them confidential and limit their use of it to the purposes for which we send it to them, such as notifying you of special offers. We also provide information about you to others as permitted or required by law for specific, limited purposes, such as processing transactions you request (towing, DMV), responding to subpoenas or government agencies.

**Information protection.** We protect nonpublic personal information about you by restricting access to those employees who need to know. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard this nonpublic personal information.

**This notice is provided on behalf of:**  
Automobile Club of Southern California  
AAA Club Services, LLC  
ACSC Management Services, Inc. 

Note: The words "you," and "your," as used in this notice, mean an individual, including a former customer, who seeks to obtain, obtains, or has obtained a product or service from the Auto Club or an affiliate that is to be used primarily for personal, family or household purposes.

## Online Practices

**Web site information.** We collect information from our web site that you give to us, and use it to facilitate your requests, process your transactions, and/or update your account.

Our web servers record your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the pages you visit while at our site. We use this information for internal tracking purposes, to enhance your experience on our site, to respond to your requests, and to advise you of services and products.

We also collect information from your browser software in order to properly display information and for statistical purposes, but we do not use this information to identify you.

Secure transactions are accomplished with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to assure that your data is safely communicated to us.

**Email Addresses.** If you give us your email address, we may email you offers (e.g., travel or insurance) for products and services that may be of interest to you. With each such offer you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future marketing emails. Even if you opt-out, we reserve the right to email you for non-marketing purposes.

**Use of "Cookies."** We use a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" (small file placed on the user’s hard drive) to facilitate site navigation, Internet sessions, and to maintain security. For example, we use cookies to remember your personal settings, pre-fill forms for you, and to monitor your use of our web site to improve our services. If you choose not to enable cookies on your browser, you will not be able to use some of the services offered on our web site.

We also use cookies and “web beacons” (also referred to as pixel tags, 1x1s, or transparent GIFs) to manage our email programs. These tags gather information to analyze the performance of our email marketing and help us understand how consumers respond to our messages.

**Information Collected by Third-Party Advertising.** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. These companies employ cookies and web beacons to gather anonymous information that permits us to analyze, modify and improve our advertising content. The information collected is not personally identifiable. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features these third-party advertising companies may use, and their information practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

## Modification of Terms

We may amend our Privacy Notice and Online Practices at any time. You should review the Privacy Notice and Online Practices from time to time to become aware of any changes. Effective date: May 7, 2009.
